What was your goal? Why go into that space knowing it could go off the rails?
Because ultimately we are in a desperate time of disinformation. Like I call this the age of
idiocy, right? And we know that when it comes to the internets, when it comes to media,
there really has just been a commitment to not telling whole truths. We know that when it comes
to academia, when it comes to nonprofits, like it's just not a truthful time. And I know that I'm
OD truthful, which is why sometimes people have an issue. But when you are of this type of mindset,
when you are a revolutionary, when you know that you have the facts, you are responsible to explain
it over and over and over again. That is a quote from the great Thomas Sankara of Burkina Faso.
And I know that about myself and many of my peers. We understand that we have to put ourselves in
these spaces sometimes and take the bruise and annoyance, knowing that we aren't speaking to
just these individuals. We're speaking to an entire audience watching who may never have heard what
we have to say and they need to.